# James Lee

jazz0910man@gmail.com +13237395458

North York, Ontario, Canada

Passionate and skilled Web & Blockchain Developer offering 8+ years of relevant experience and a proven track record of success in achieving extraordinary results. With a strong attention to detail and accuracy and the important ability to function well in a team setting, James is looking for a Web & Blockchain Developer job within a forward-moving company.

#### **Additional Information**

- skype live:.cid.9106fef336b5c354
- Telegram jazz0910man
- Discord jazzman#2006

#### Links

https://www.linkedin.com/in/james-lee-3620b6219/

https://github.com/HappyVirgo

#### **Skills**

JavaScript - 8 years

TypeScript - 3 years

Solidity, Vyper, Web3.js, Web3.py, Truffle, Hardhat - 2 years

React.js, React Native, Redux (Toolkit, Saga, Thunk), Next.js - 5 years

Vue.js, Vuex, Vuetify, Nuxt.js - 5 years

Node.js, Express.js, Nest.js - 5 years

Rest API, GraphOL - 5 years

Angular 8+ - 3 years

Bootstrap, Material UI, Chakra UI, Ant Design - 3 years

Styled-components, Tailwind CSS - 3 years

CSS/SCSS/LESS - 8 years

Jest, Enzyme, Cypress, React/Vue Testing library - 3 years

AWS, Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins, Azure - 2 years

### **Work Experience**

## Senior Blockchain Developer

11/2021 to Present

XFai

Cavman Islands

- · Built the efficient DEX system based on Etherem
- · Developed optimized, well-qualified smart contract
- · Built user interface based on the pixel-perfect design
- Integrated smart contract into the React site by using web3.js
- Unit/Integration tests using Jest, Testing library, and Cypress

## **Blockchain Developer**

07/2021 to 11/2021

Optify

Reston, Virginia, United States

- Built the DeFi adapter like the bridge that allows vaults to invest in a protocol for executing Opty.fi's network of strategies.
- · Built some DeFi adapters on the Polygon and Avalanche network using Solidity
- Interact with DEX protocols including UniswapV2, V3, Quickswap, etc
- · Unit/Integration tests using Hardhat, Web3 libraries

## PM & Lead Developer

08/2020 to 02/2021

Project AI

Australia

- Engaged in Liquid mode development using React, Hooks, Context, Typescript, React-query, Storybook, Styled-components, React Testing Library, and Cypress, Django, Rest Framework, Postgresgl
- Built restful api to get statistic data for surveys of project
- · Built user interface based on the pixel-perfect design

- Data visualization with Rechart and D3.is
- Unit/Integration tests using Jest, Testing library, and Cypress

## **Front-end Developer**

05/2019 to 03/2020

Ecotrak Facility Management Software

Irvine, California, United States

- Developed a task management platform with React, Chakra UI, Redux Toolkit, Typescript, GraphQL, Jest, Enzyme, etc
- Developed reusable/scalable components with Storybook
- Structured a global Redux store using the Redux toolkit and data fetching and caching layer using RTK guery
- Implemented Drag& Drop with React-dnd in the task board
- API integration using Apollo GraphOL and unit testing with Jest and Enzyme

### **Full-stack Developer**

07/2017 to 01/2019

Allhirds

San Francisco, California, United States

- Developed an e-commerce platform using Node.js, Express.js, Microservices, Vue.js, Vuex, Typescript, Jenkins, AWS
- Designed micro-service structure and developed Restful APIs
- Did automation tests on developed API endpoints and distributed API documentation among developers
- Established CI/CD pipelines using Jenkins, Github, and AWS
- Developed e-commerce components and web pages based on pixel-perfect design.

## Web Developer

03/2015 to 03/2017

Weedmaps

Irvine, California, United States

- Developed a delivery logistics platform using Vue.js, Javascript, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Websocket, etc.
- Developed a customer website where customers can track their job status
- · Built dashboards for company owners to manage jobs and drivers and automate & optimize routes
- Migrated web pages in PHP into Vue.is
- Implemented real-time location tracking using google maps and web socket.

#### Education

## **University of Buenos Aires**

Bachelor's Computer Science Buenos Aires, Argentina 09/2011 to 09/2014